<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="terms">Terms</string>
    <string name="eula">
This is your agreement for using the SoundRec program.
If you don\'t agree with it, don\'t install or, if it\'s too late,
uninstall the software.  

The program is free software and is open source. Everyone who has
a device capable of running it is allowed to run it, to share it,
without cost.

You agree that the providers of this software are not responsible
for anything at all that happens while or because of running it,
including software bugs, corruption of data, traffic accidents
however caused, or any other incident however caused.
Do not operate a vehicle while manipulating this program.
\n
Copyright © 2008-2015 Ian F. Darwin. All rights reserved.
\n
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:\n
1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.\n
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
   documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.\n

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE AUTHOR AND CONTRIBUTORS \`\`AS IS\'\' AND
ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE
IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE
ARE DISCLAIMED.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE
FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL
DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS
OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION)
HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT
LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY
OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF
SUCH DAMAGE.

The name "SoundRec" is a trademark and may not be used to refer to
another application.
</string>
</resources>
